<resources>
    <string-array name="language_code_list" translatable="false">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>bn</item> <!-- 孟加拉语 -->
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="language_codetz_list" translatable="false">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>sw</item> <!-- 坦桑语 -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- permission_spec_titles和permission_spec_contents数量要一致-->
    <string-array name="permission_spec_titles">
        <item>Personal information:</item>
        <item>Location:</item>
        <item>Camera:</item>
<!--        <item>Calendar:</item>-->
        <item>App list:</item>
<!--        <item>SMS Information:</item>-->
        <item>Contact:</item>
        <item>Device:</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="permission_spec_contents">
        <item>When you use the app, we will ask you to enter some necessary personal information to identify your true identity and verify your credit score, etc. The purpose of doing so is to better identify and provide you with exclusive credit limits. At the same time, in order to protect your fund security, the information we need to collect includes but is not limited to: your name, bank card information, BVN number, your emergency contact number, your work situation, your address, etc. You can rest assured that we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations without your permission, nor will we provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server: https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>
        <item>When you use the app, we will apply for permission to obtain your location and obtain your current location. The purpose of doing so is to ensure that you apply for a loan in a safe environment , and also to protect your funds. Similarly, when you fill in the information and apply for a loan, we will once again request permission to obtain your location to ensure the safety of your funds. You can rest assured that we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations without your permission, nor will we provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server:https://api.drutocash.store ncryption protection</item>
        <item>When you use the app, we will ask you to grant us the permission to open the mobile phone camera , the purpose of the request is for you to better fill in your personal information, so that we can confirm that you are the person applying for a loan, and evaluate your credit score. This permission will only take effect when you fill in your personal information and take a photo. You can rest assured that without your permission, we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations or provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server: https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>
<!--        <item>We collect and use your calendar data.\n-->
<!--Purpose: To remind users before they payments are due and to avoid a drop in their credit score due to overdue payments.\n-->
<!--You can rest assured that without your permission, we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations or provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server: https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>-->
        <item>In order to ensure that your funds are truly safe, when you use our app to apply for a loan, we will request and access the data in your phone, collect and query whether there are malicious software or irregular apps that endanger your information security. If such software exists, it may affect your personal credit and loan progress. You can rest assured that without your permission, we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations or provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server: https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>
<!--        <item>Purpose of obtaining SMS permissions:\n-->
<!--In order to better analyze the user\'s financial situation, more accurately evaluate the user\'s credit limit, push suitable loan products to users, continuously optimize our applications, and provide more suitable review strategies for more Tanzanian citizens who need funds.-->
<!--Scope of SMS access:\n-->
<!--Druto Cash responds to Google\'s policy on collecting user SMS, we strictly limit the scope of SMS access, and only obtain financial information involving the following financial fields:\'salio\',\'tsh\',\'pesa\',\'piga\',\'malipo\',\'mkopo\',\'kutoka\',\'tarehe\',\'umepokea\',\'mteja\',\'tafadhali\',\'Akaunti\',\'imethibitishwa\',\'Kumbukumbu\',\'kulipa\',\'TZS\',\'yamepokelewa\',\'lipa\',\'umelipia\',\'lako\',\'betPawa\'-->
<!--\'loan\',\'balance\',\'VAT\',\'account\',\'Transaction\',\'amount\',\'received\',\'fee\',\'repayment\',\'financial\',\'paid\'\n-->
<!--SMS data security:\n-->
<!--We will not share this data with any third party, the data will be uploaded to the server:\n-->
<!--https://api.drutocash.store and deleted regularly</item>-->
        <item>In order to ensure the safety of your and our funds, when you apply for a loan, we will ask you to fill in several contact information of your friends or family members to help you complete the loan process. You can rest assured that without your permission, we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations or provide it any third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server:https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>
        <item>We will obtain your device information. Collect and monitor specific information about your device including your device name, model, region and language settings, device identification code, device hardware and software information, status, usage habits, unique device identifiers like IMEI and serial number to uniquely identify the device and ensure that unauthorized devices are not to act on your behalf to prevent frauds.This will help us to identify your user portrait and preferences and to recommend the suitable products.You can rest assured that without your permission, we will not use this information for any non-compliant operations or provide it to third parties. We will upload it to a dedicated server: https://api.drutocash.store for encryption protection</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
